Experimental College Records UA044
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Explorations and Perspectives, 1967 -- 2000; UA044.002; 6.75 Linear Feet
  - Explorations, 1991 -- 2000; UA044.002.033 (Box 33)
    In November 2015, student applications to lead Perspectives seminars, 1991-2000, were removed and confidentially destroyed. Application packets included: Personal information sheets, transcripts, application essays, faculty recommendations, supplemental letters of recommendation, and Academic Advisor references.
- Course files, 1965 -- 2012; UA044.003; 22.8 Linear Feet
  This series contains files on courses taught in the Experimental College from 1966. Files contain course catalog description form and may contain syllabi, copies of handouts, and copies of evaluation forms. Experimental college courses are taught by faculty, staff, interested outsiders. Applications are submitted to the Experimental College board. S means spring, F means fall. Full course description available in the bulletins.
  This series is arranged by course number.
  This series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This series may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
  - EXP 001 F'70 Richard Wright: The Man and His Works, 1970; UA044.003.010.00001; Smith, Glenn (Box 10)
  - EXP 001 S S'72 The Writings of Nabokov, 1972; UA044.003.010.00002; Ryder, Mark (Box 10)
  - EXP 001 F F'72 Fairy Tales, Fables and Myths, 1972; UA044.003.010.00003; Nieder, Erika D. (Box 10)
  - EXP 001 F F'74 Popular Fiction, 1974; UA044.003.010.00004; Slavitt, David R. (Box 10)
  - EXP 001 F'75 Writing of Oral Literature, 1975; UA044.003.010.00005; Lockwood, Sebastian (Box 10)
  - EXP 001 S S'76 Allegory: The Hidden Language, 1976; UA044.003.010.00006; Storch, Margaret (Box 10)
  - EXP 002 F'75 Vonnegut and Brautigan, 1975; UA044.003.010.00007; Bove, Anthony L. (Box 10)
  - EXP 002 S S'75 Modern Greek Literature, 1975; UA044.003.010.00008; Prousis, Theophilus C. (Box 10)
  - EXP 002 S S'74 Suicide and Modern Poetry, 1974; UA044.003.010.00009; Howard, Hugh G. (Box 10)
  - EXP 002 S S'72 Kerouac and His Circle of Friends, 1972; UA044.003.010.00010; Raphael, David (Box 10)
  - EXP 002 S'70 Autobiography in the Twentieth Century:The Self as History and Myth, 1970; UA044.003.010.00011; Jacob, Eva (Box 10)
  - EXP 002 F F'72 The Homosexual in Literature, 1972; UA044.003.010.00012; Ratner, Ellen F.; Kleitz, Katherine (Box 10)
  - EXP 002 S'67 Literature in Chaos, 1967; UA044.003.010.00013 (Box 10)
  - EXP 003 F'75 Rock Music '64-'74, 1975; UA044.003.010.00014; Lindgren, Erik (Box 10)
  - EXP 003 S S'74 From Expessionism to Discovery, 1974; UA044.003.010.00015; Perry, John (Box 10)
  - EXP 003 F F'74 Flatonic and Erotic Love, UA044.003.010.00016; Steindler, Mariangela C. (Box 10)
  - EXP 003 S S'73 The Best Seller: Popular Literature in America, 1973; UA044.003.010.00017; Kaslow, Daniel (Box 10)
  - EXP 003 F'73 Becket's Onion, 1973; UA044.003.010.00018; Hanlin, John (Box 10)
  - EXP 003 F'72 Hollywood Literature, 1973; UA044.003.010.00019; Chipman, Bruce (Box 10)
  - EXP 003 S S'72 The Super-Hero Comic Book, 1973; UA044.003.010.00020; Harman, Paul; Sawyer, Arnie (Box 10)
  - EXP 003 S F'70 Poetry: Beat and Otherwise, 1970; UA044.003.010.00021; Brennan, John Michael (Box 10)
  - EXP 004S S'74 20th Century Writing: The Experimentors, 1974; UA044.003.010.00022; Hanlin, John (Box 10)
  - EXP 004 F'75 Jazz and Its Revolution (1850-1975), UA044.003.010.00023; Hanlin, John (Box 10)
  - EXP 004 F'72 Contemporary Technical Painting, 1975; UA044.003.010.00024; Macomber, Steven (Box 10)
  - EXP 004 S S'73 Satiric Art of Evelyn Waugh, 1973; UA044.003.010.00025; Peter, Tracy (Box 10)
  - EXP 004 S S'72 Listening to Symphonic Music, 1973; UA044.003.010.00026; Rothstein, Joseph (Box 10)
  - EXP 004 S'71 Short Fiction: Mechanics and Experience, 1971; UA044.003.010.00027; Slattery, John (Box 10)
  - EXP 004 F'65 S'66 Information Communication and Knowledge, 1965 -- 1966; UA044.003.010.00028; Batteau, Dwight W. (Box 10)
  - EXP 005 F'75 Movies, 1975; UA044.003.010.00029; Moran, Richard (Box 10)
  - EXP 005 S'75 Comedy Light and Dark, 1975; UA044.003.010.00030; Frail, David (Box 10)
  - EXP 005F F'74 Visions of Latin America, 1974; UA044.003.010.00031; Sedgwick, Tony (Box 10)
  - EXP 005S S'74 Inner-Twining, 1974; UA044.003.010.00032; Koch, Liz (Box 10)
  - EXP 005F F'73 Five Centuries of Prints, 1973; UA044.003.010.00033; Faxon, Alicia (Box 10)
  - EXP 005S S'73 Fantastic Figures, 1973; UA044.003.010.00034; Angell, George; Hill, Jeff (Box 10)
  - EXP 005F F'72 Ethnomusicology, 1972; UA044.003.010.00035; Titon, Jeff (Box 10)
  - EXP 005S S'72 Dramatic Analysis, 1972; UA044.003.010.00036; Westwood, Jefferson (Box 10)
  - EXP 005 F'70 American Women Poets, 1970; UA044.003.010.00037; Braun, Tommie A. (Box 10)
  - EXP 006 S'75 Blake: His Works of Art, 1975; UA044.003.010.00038; Gabriella, Katherine (Box 10)
  - EXP 006F F'72 Chinese Literature in Translation, 1972; UA044.003.010.00039; Chude, Fannie (Box 10)
  - EXP 006S S'71 Charles Dickens: His Life and Works, 1971; UA044.003.010.00040; Lewis, Ron (Box 10)
  - EXP 006F F'73 Silversmithing and Enamelling, 1973; UA044.003.010.00041; Juran, Daryl (Box 10)
  - EXP 006s F'72 Science Fiction, 1972; UA044.003.010.00042; Chang, Nelson (Box 10)
  - EXP 006 S'70 Contemporary World Poetry, 1970; UA044.003.010.00043; Chang, Nelson (Box 10)
  - EXP 007 F'75 Color Phot Through Slide Medium, 1975; UA044.003.010.00044; Quan, Richard (Box 10)
  - EXP 007S S'75 History and the Novel, 1975; UA044.003.010.00045; Allen, James (Box 10)
  - EXP 007F F'74 History and the Novel, 1974; UA044.003.010.00046; Schatz, Linda (Box 10)
  - EXP 007S S'73 Great Fantasy Novels, 1974; UA044.003.010.00047; Cody, David (Box 10)
  - EXP 007 F'73 Chinese Calligraphy, 1973; UA044.003.010.00048; Chan, Kai P. (Box 10)
  - EXP 007 F'66 Education of Disadvantaged Youth, 1966; UA044.003.010.00049 (Box 10)
  - EXP 007 F'71 Religious Themes in Science Fiction, 1971; UA044.003.010.00050; Smith, Andrew (Box 10)
  - EXP 008 S'75 Psychology Applied Through Creative Writing, 1975; UA044.003.010.00051; Smith, Cindy (Box 10)
  - EXP 008S S'74 Color: As Symbol and Aesthetic, 1974; UA044.003.010.00052; Oberdorfer, Jeff (Box 10)
  - EXP 008 F'75 Trends in American Painting and Photography, 1975; UA044.003.010.00053; Brown, Judith (Box 10)
  - EXP 008 F'73 Movement and Masks, 1973; UA044.003.010.00054; Guzzetti, Deborah (Box 10)
  - EXP 008 S'73 Body English, 1973; UA044.003.010.00055; Dixon, Carl (Box 10)
  - EXP 008 S'72 Dilemmas of the 20th Century II, 1972; UA044.003.010.00056; Kochansky, Chris (Box 10)
  - EXP 008 S'66 Workshop in Creativity, 1966; UA044.003.010.00057 (Box 10)
  - EXP 008 and 080 F'68, S'69, F'69, S'70 Introduction to Scholarship, 1968 -- 1970; UA044.003.010.00058 (Box 10)
  - EXP 009 F65 Prelude to the Absurd, 1965; UA044.003.010.00059 (Box 10)
  - EXP 010 Spring 75, Fall 75 Inner-Twining, 1975; UA044.003.010.00060; Koch, Liz (Box 10)
  - EXP 010F Fall 74 Performing in Masks, 1974; UA044.003.010.00061; Fortson, Deborah (Box 10)
  - EXP 010S Spring 74 Pantomime, 1974; UA044.003.010.00062; Rijke, Christina (Box 10)
  - EXP 011 F75, F76 Spinning and Dyeing, 1975 -- 1976; UA044.003.010.00063; Rijke, Christina (Box 10)
  - EXP 011F Fall 74 Beethoven, 1974; UA044.003.010.00064; Hiebert, Elfrieda (Box 10)
  - EXP 011S Spring 75 Landscape Painting, 1975; UA044.003.010.00065; Hutter, Alice; Simonds, Alice (Box 10)
    Fall 1975
  - EXP 011S Spring 74 Country Roots: Southern Folk Songs, 1974; UA044.003.010.00066; Hyslop, Stephen (Box 10)
  - EXP 011S Spring 73 Short Story Workshop, 1973; UA044.003.010.00067; Shilepsk, Nancy (Box 10)
  - EXP 011S Spring 72 Social and Economic Aspects of Malnutrition, 1972; UA044.003.010.00068; Pakiszegi, Nasrin (Box 10)
  - EXP 011 F71 Intro to 360 Aniscobol Programming, 1971; UA044.003.010.00069; Afentakis, Nicholas (Box 10)
  - EXP 011 S71 Computers and Programming: Concepts and Practice, 1971; UA044.003.010.00070; Detroy, Doug (Box 10)
  - EXP 011 F70 A Non-technical Introduction to Computer Programming, 1970; UA044.003.010.00071; Neslter, Eric (Box 10)
  - EXP 011 S66 Humanism in Science, 1966; UA044.003.010.00072; Illinger, K.H. (Box 10)
  - EXP 012 F75 Arts Management Needs You, 1975; UA044.003.010.00073; Friedi, Max (Box 10)
  - EXP 012 Spring 75 Songs and Songwriters, 1975; UA044.003.010.00074; Nininger, William (Box 10)
  - EXP 012S S72 Environment and Society, 1972; UA044.003.010.00075; Rosenthal, Jon (Box 10)
  - EXP 012 S70 Astrophysics, 1970; UA044.003.010.00076; Ferruzzi, Arthur (Box 10)
  - EXP 013S S'74 The Harpsichord, 1974; UA044.003.010.00077; Kreifeldt, Winifred (Box 10)
  - EXP 013S S'72 Towards a More Rational Federal Housing Policy, 1972; UA044.003.010.00078; Morris, Peter (Box 10)
  - EXP 013 F'68 An Evening of Eurythmy, 1968; UA044.003.010.00079; Aldan, Daisy (Box 10)
  - EXP 013 S'69 Experimental Workshop in Yoga for the West, 1969; UA044.003.010.00080; Boyles, Peg (Box 10)
  - EXP 075F F'74 Law and the Family, 1974; UA044.003.011.00001; Jackson, Marie O. (Box 11)
  - EXP 014 F'75 Life and Living, 1975; UA044.003.011.00002; Miller, Robert L'H. (Box 11)
  - EXP 014S S'72 Health Care System: Analysis and Alternatives, 1972; UA044.003.011.00003; Schwartz, Andrew; Levison, Judy; Schiff, Gordon (Box 11)
  - EXP 014 S'70 IBM Programming Language, 1970; UA044.003.011.00004; Saltier, Jack (Box 11)
  - EXP 014S S'75 Noh Theatre and Zen, 1975; UA044.003.011.00005; Munakata, Kuniyoshi (Box 11)
  - EXP 014 S'71 Introduction to 1130 Fortran Programming, 1971; UA044.003.011.00006; Ekiert, George (Box 11)
  - EXP 015F F'75 The Male Experience, 1975; UA044.003.011.00007; Karesky, Raymond (Box 11)
  - EXP 015F F'73 Poetry of Sexual Roles, 1973; UA044.003.011.00008; Bass, Ellen (Box 11)
  - EXP 015 S&F'66, S&F'67, S&F'68, S&F'69, S&F'70 Auditing for Breadth, 1966 -- 1970; UA044.003.011.00009; Van Wormer, Kenneth A. (Box 11)
  - EXP 016S S'74 Psychology of Women, 1974; UA044.003.011.00010; Clark, Michele (Box 11)
  - EXP 016F F'73 Psychology and Women, 1973; UA044.003.011.00011; Henley, Nancy (Box 11)
  - EXP 016S S'72 Health Crisis: Call to Action, 1972; UA044.003.011.00012; Korkosz, Tanya; Lorman, Constance; Schoedel, Delores (Box 11)
  - EXP 016 F'75 Sex Roles: Our Expanding Awareness, 1975; UA044.003.011.00013; Watson, Neill; Cory, Thayer (Box 11)
  - EXP 017S S&F'75 Our Bodies, Ourselves, 1975; UA044.003.011.00014; Ditzion, Joan (Box 11)
  - EXP 017S S&F'74 Our Bodies, Ourselves, 1974; UA044.003.011.00015; Hawley, Nancy (Box 11)
  - EXP 017S S'72 Science, Technology and Public Policy, 1972; UA044.003.011.00016; Nolfi, George Jr. (Box 11)
  - EXP 017 S'69 Chemistry for the Curious, 1969; UA044.003.011.00017; Urry, Grant (Box 11)
  - EXP 018S F'74 Behavioral Analysis Women's Roles, 1974; UA044.003.011.00018; Brauer, Shelley (Box 11)
  - EXP 018 F'75 The Control of Sleep, 1975; UA044.003.011.00019; Ware, Catesby (Box 11)
  - EXP 018S S'74 Exploring Black Womenhood, 1974; UA044.003.011.00020; Williams, Barbara; Berry, Frances (Box 11)
  - EXP 018F F'74 Women in Cross-Cultural Perspectives, 1974; UA044.003.011.00021; Mackoff, Barbara (Box 11)
  - EXP 018S S'73 Women in Changing Societies, 1973; UA044.003.011.00022; McAfee, Kathy (Box 11)
  - EXP 018S S'72 Legal Aspects of Enviromental Quality, 1972; UA044.003.011.00023; Stern, James (Box 11)
  - EXP 018 S'67 Seminar in Humanism and Science, 1967; UA044.003.011.00024; Illinger, Karl H. (Box 11)
  - EXP 018 S&F'71 Bird Migration, 1971; UA044.003.011.00025; Payson, Harold III (Box 11)
  - EXP 019S S&F'73 Women's Liberation, 1973; UA044.003.011.00026; Messina, Denise (Box 11)
  - EXP 019 F'75 EEG, The Brain and Psychology, 1975; UA044.003.011.00027; Skoff, Barry (Box 11)
  - EXP 019S S'75 Women in Medieval Society, 1975; UA044.003.011.00028; Kaiser, Barbara (Box 11)
  - EXP 019F F'74 Women and Revolution, 1974; UA044.003.011.00029; Leighton, Marion (Box 11)
  - EXP 019S S'74 Women Record Their Lives, 1974; UA044.003.011.00030; Gane, Gill (Box 11)
  - EXP 019 F'70 Visual Perception, 1970; UA044.003.011.00031; Gane, Gill (Box 11)
  - EXP 019 F'67 Visual Perception, 1967; UA044.003.011.00032; Elioseff, L.A (Box 11)
  - EXP 020 S'73 Hieroglyphics, 1973; UA044.003.011.00033; Elioseff, L.A (Box 11)
  - EXP 020 S'70 The Mystical Tradition, 1970; UA044.003.011.00034; Politte, Marni; Braun, Tommie Ann (Box 11)
  - EXP 021 S'72, S'74 Teaching English as a Foreign Language, 1972 -- 1974; UA044.003.011.00035; Politte, Marni; Braun, Tommie Ann (Box 11)
  - EXP 020 S'71 Hatha Yoga, 1971; UA044.003.011.00036; Paige, Judy (Box 11)
  - EXP 021 F'72,S73, F73,S74,F74,S75,F75,S76 Teaching English as a Foreign Language, 1972 -- 1976; UA044.003.011.00037; Booker, Margaret (Box 11)
    75 years from date of creation.
  - EXP 21 F69,S70,F70,S71 Introduction to Choreography, 1969 -- 1971; UA044.003.011.00038; Rapoport, Patricia (Box 11)
  - EXP 21 F71 Contemporary Dance Techniques, 1971; UA044.003.011.00039; White, Griselda (Box 11)
  - EXP 22S S74 Modern Portuguese, 1974; UA044.003.011.00040; White, Paul (Box 11)
  - EXP 22S F75 Intro to Romanian Language and Culture, 1975; UA044.003.011.00041; Andronesen, Victor (Box 11)
  - EXP 22S Spring 73, Fall 73 Conversational Japanese, 1973; UA044.003.011.00042; Kau, Chuan (Box 11)
  - EXP 22S S72 Elementary Mandarin Chinese, 1972; UA044.003.011.00043; Chen, Hui-ping (Box 11)
  - EXP 22 S71 Modern Mysticism, UA044.003.011.00044; Sprich, Robert (Box 11)
  - EXP 22 S70 Transcendental Experience, 1970; UA044.003.011.00045; Stevens, David (Box 11)
  - EXP 23 S72 Advanced Mandarin Chinese, 1972; UA044.003.011.00046; Ching, Yu-pei (Box 11)
  - EXP 23 F69 Autobiography, 1969; UA044.003.011.00047; Jacob, Eva (Box 11)
  - EXP 23 F71 I Ching, 1971; UA044.003.011.00048; Charry, David (Box 11)
  - EXP 24 S72, F72 Elementary Modern Greek, 1972; UA044.003.011.00049; Anagnostopoulos, Athan (Box 11)
  - EXP 24 S71 Topics in Aesthetics, 1971; UA044.003.011.00050; Ross, Roger (Box 11)
  - EXP 024F and 025S F73,S74,F75,S76,F78 Egyptian Hieroglyphics I,II, 1973 -- 1978; UA044.003.011.00051; Kaczmarczyk, Alexander (Box 11)
  - EXP 025F F72 Modern Greek II, 1972; UA044.003.011.00052; Anagnostopoulos, Athan (Box 11)
  - EXP 025F F71 Evil, Adversity, and Horrow, 1971; UA044.003.011.00053; Dallery, Carleton (Box 11)
  - EXP 025 F70 Astrological Studies, 1970; UA044.003.011.00054; Williams, Peter (Box 11)
  - EXP 026 F75 Tubingen At Tufts, 1975; UA044.003.011.00055; Collins, Joy; Padula, Carol (Box 11)
  - EXP 026F F73 Elementary Swahili, 1973; UA044.003.011.00056; Kenya, Peter (Box 11)
  - EXP 026S S73 Modern Greek III, 1973; UA044.003.011.00057; Anagnostopoulos, Athan (Box 11)
  - EXP 026 F70 God and Man: Approaches to Classical Judaism, 1970; UA044.003.011.00058; Green, Art (Box 11)
  - EXP 027 F75 Jewish Mysticism, 1975; UA044.003.011.00059; Rosenberg, Joel (Box 11)
  - EXP 027F F72 Sanskrit I, 1972; UA044.003.011.00060; Willinder, W. E. (Box 11)
  - EXP 027 F69 Psychoanalysis and Literature, 1969; UA044.003.011.00061; Sprich, Robert (Box 11)
  - EXP 028S S73 Sanskrit II, 1973; UA044.003.011.00062; Willinder, W. E. (Box 11)
  - EXP 028 F70 Theories of Racism, 1970; UA044.003.011.00063; Daniels, Norman (Box 11)
  - EXP 029 Tibet: A Study in Religious Culture, 1971; UA044.003.011.00064; Reddy, Dan (Box 11)
  - EXP 029 F69 Comparative Forms of Radio Programming, 1969; UA044.003.011.00065; Trodella, Richard (Box 11)
  - EXP 030 S72, F72 Revolutionary Men in History, 1972; UA044.003.011.00066; Meltzer, Roger (Box 11)
  - EXP 030 S71 Modern Jewish Thought, 1971; UA044.003.011.00067; Rosenberg, Joel (Box 11)
  - EXP 030 F70 Excursions into Mathematics for Undergraduate Tutors, 1970; UA044.003.011.00068; Schlesinger, James (Box 11)
  - EXP 031-034 F65, S66, F66, S67, F67 Introductory and Interdisciplinary Courses in the Natural Sciences, 1965 -- 1967; UA044.003.011.00069; Crook, Dorothea J. (Box 11)
  - EXP 031F F72 Five Legal Case Histories, 1972; UA044.003.011.00070; Conkling, Chris (Box 11)
  - EXP 031 F71 Documentary Film Production, 1971; UA044.003.011.00071; Reed, Theodore (Box 11)
  - EXP 032S S75 Massachusetts Corrections Today, 1975; UA044.003.012.00001; Bogdanchik, Robert (Box 12)
  - EXP 032F F72 Mass. Courts and Corrections, 1972; UA044.003.012.00002; Habib, Phyllis; DeGelleke, Peter (Box 12)
  - EXP 032S S72 The Black "Conversation" Experience, 1972; UA044.003.012.00003; Edison, Kenneth (Box 12)
  - EXP 032 F71 Creative Verbal Media, 1971; UA044.003.012.00004; Brodman, Richard (Box 12)
  - EXP 033S S74 Factory Folklore, 1974; UA044.003.012.00005; Nickerson, Bruce (Box 12)
  - EXP 033F F73 Cultural Ecology, 1973; UA044.003.012.00006; Russell, Ellen (Box 12)
  - EXP 033S S73 19th Century Armenian Culture, 1973; UA044.003.012.00007; Megerdichian, Richard (Box 12)
  - EXP 033F F72 Young Workers, 1972; UA044.003.012.00008; Blumenthal, Sidney (Box 12)
  - EXP 033S S72 The Plains Indians, 1972; UA044.003.012.00009; Haas, Marian (Box 12)
  - EXP 033 F71 Dilemmas of the 20th Century, 1971; UA044.003.012.00010; Kochansky, Chris (Box 12)
  - EXP 034S S75 Hospitals and Their Reorganization, 1975; UA044.003.012.00011; Vena, Carl (Box 12)
  - EXP 034S S74 The Way of the Samurai, 1974; UA044.003.012.00012; Akiba, Tadatoshi (Box 12)
  - EXP 034S S73 Protest and Rebellion, 1973; UA044.003.012.00013; Wasserstrom, Robert (Box 12)
  - EXP 034S S72 American Cultural Revolution, 1972; UA044.003.012.00014; Paulson, Robert; Greisman, Gordon (Box 12)
  - EXP 035F F73 Social Roots of Latin American Folksong, 1973; UA044.003.012.00015; Halperin, Ernest (Box 12)
  - EXP 035F F72 Law and Individual in Society, 1972; UA044.003.012.00016; Goodstein, Gerald (Box 12)
  - EXP 035S S72 Nazi and Soviet Anti-Semitism, 1972; UA044.003.012.00017; Delfiner, Henry (Box 12)
  - EXP 035 F71 The Spanish Civil War, 1971; UA044.003.012.00018; Bagge, Michael (Box 12)
  - EXP 035 S69 Non-History: The Spanish Civil War, 1969; UA044.003.012.00019; Harwood, Victor; Opal. Kitridge (Box 12)
  - EXP 036S S75 Responsible Lifestyles, 1975; UA044.003.012.00020; Keese, Stephen A.; Atkinson, Jeannette (Box 12)
  - EXP 036S S74 Ancient Egypt, 1974; UA044.003.012.00021; Kaczmarczyk, Alex (Box 12)
  - EXP 036F F72 South American Indians, 1972; UA044.003.012.00022; Ruff, Jacquelynn (Box 12)
  - EXP 036S S72 The Heritage of Babylon, 1972; UA044.003.012.00023; Kaczmarczyk, Alex (Box 12)
  - EXP 036 S70 The Future of Our Environment, 1970; UA044.003.012.00024; Kroesser, F. William (Box 12)
  - EXP 037 F77, S75 The Male Experience, 1975 -- 1977; UA044.003.012.00025; Karesky, Raymond (Box 12)
  - EXP 037S S73 East Africa, 1973; UA044.003.012.00026; Gramly, Michael (Box 12)
  - EXP 037F F73 Dormitory as a Social System, 1973; UA044.003.012.00027; Murdock, Maggi; Murdock, Nick (Box 12)
  - EXP 037 F72 Sports in America, 1972; UA044.003.012.00028; Schwebel, Robert (Box 12)
  - EXP 037S S72 Sexim and the Familiy, 1972; UA044.003.012.00029; Arnold, Patricia; Shearer, Derek (Box 12)
  - EXP 037 F69 Appalachian Poverty, 1969; UA044.003.012.00030 (Box 12)
  - EXP 038S S75 Kentucky, Eastern, 1975; UA044.003.012.00031 (Box 12)
  - EXP 038 S72, F72 Changing Attitudes Towards Homosexuality, 1972; UA044.003.012.00032; Lawrence, John (Box 12)
  - EXP 038S S80 Who? What?, and Why? of Gifted Education, 1980; UA044.003.012.00033; Stolow, Constance (Box 12)
  - EXP 038S S74 The Western Hermetic Tradition, 1974; UA044.003.012.00034; O'Donnell, John (Box 12)
  - EXP 038F F73 The 1950's, 1973; UA044.003.012.00035; Young, Allen (Box 12)
  - EXP 038 F70 Organic Form, 1970; UA044.003.012.00036; Jacobs, Eva (Box 12)
  - EXP 039S S74 The Napoleonic Era, 1974; UA044.003.012.00037; Howell, Thomas; Waldbauer, Richard (Box 12)
  - EXP 039S S73 Myth and Ritual, 1973; UA044.003.012.00038; Ewing, Kathy (Box 12)
  - EXP 039F F72 Analysis of Social Doctrine In Contemporary Issues, 1972; UA044.003.012.00039; Williams, Ken (Box 12)
  - EXP 039 F69 Medical Care, 1969; UA044.003.012.00040; Jaffe, Kenneth Marc (Box 12)
  - EXP 040S S75 Military History Since 1700, 1975; UA044.003.012.00041; Weinburg, Mark (Box 12)
  - EXP 040S S74 Black Nationalism and White Radicalism, 1974; UA044.003.012.00042; Warren, Maurie (Box 12)
  - EXP 040S S73 Beginning Choreography, 1973; UA044.003.012.00043; White, Griselda (Box 12)
  - EXP 040F F72 Ballet: Theme and Variations, 1972; UA044.003.012.00044; White, Griselda (Box 12)
  - EXP 040S S72 Dance for Men, 1972; UA044.003.012.00045; Streep, Harry (Box 12)
  - EXP 040S S71 Ocean and Man, 1971; UA044.003.012.00046; Bergman, Pamela (Box 12)
  - EXP 041 F75 Whales, Dolphins and Man, 1975; UA044.003.012.00047; Schlinger, Barney (Box 12)
  - EXP 041S S73 Performing Dance Group, 1973; UA044.003.012.00048; White, Griselda (Box 12)
  - EXP 041F F72 Dance: Motion, Space, Time Techniques, 1972; UA044.003.012.00049; White, Griselda (Box 12)
  - EXP 041S S72 Advanced Technique, 1972; UA044.003.012.00050; White, Griselda (Box 12)
  - EXP 041 S68 Romanticism in Music and Literature, 1968; UA044.003.012.00051 (Box 12)
  - EXP 041 S71 Introduction to Contemporary Electronic and Avant-Garde Music, 1971; UA044.003.012.00052; Ryder, Mark (Box 12)
  - EXP 041F F71 Interpretive Dance, 1971; UA044.003.012.00053; Dawson, Linda; Thompson, Renee (Box 12)
  - EXP 042S S73 Corners, Curves, and Kumquats, 1973; UA044.003.012.00054; Teitebaum, Larry (Box 12)
  - EXP 042S S75 Historical Roots Soviet Society, 1975; UA044.003.012.00055; Zlotnik, Mark (Box 12)
  - EXP 042F F72 Creative Movement Improvisation, 1972; UA044.003.012.00056; White, Griselda (Box 12)
  - EXP 042S S72 Beginning Choreography, 1972; UA044.003.012.00057; White, Griselda (Box 12)
  - EXP 042 S70 Workshop in Jazz and Rock, 1970; UA044.003.012.00058; Saunders, Richard (Box 12)
  - EXP 042 S70, F70, S71 Choreography II, 1970 -- 1971; UA044.003.012.00059; Rapoport, Patricia (Box 12)
  - EXP 042 F71 In Motion, 1971; UA044.003.012.00060; White, Griselda (Box 12)
  - EXP 043 F75 World Agriculture, 1975; UA044.003.012.00061; Gray, Heather (Box 12)
  - EXP 043S S73 Freedom in Dance, 1973; UA044.003.012.00062; Weathers, Ellen (Box 12)
  - EXP 043S S72 Advanced Choreography, 1972; UA044.003.012.00063; White, Griselda (Box 12)
  - EXP 043 F71 Choreography for Performance, 1971; UA044.003.012.00064; White, Griselda (Box 12)
  - EXP 043 F67 Dance as an Art Form, 1967; UA044.003.012.00065; Steinbock, Bonnie (Box 12)
  - EXP 043 F70, S71 Choreography III, 1970 -- 1971; UA044.003.012.00066; White, Griselda (Box 12)
  - EXP 044S F73 Traditions of Dance, 1973; UA044.003.012.00067; Gorstein, Susana (Box 12)
  - EXP 044 S71 Politics and The Media, 1971; UA044.003.012.00068; Zelin, Mark; Fox, James (Box 12)
  - EXP 044 F71 Music, Art, and Dance, 1971; UA044.003.012.00069; Appleby, Audrey; Bridgman, Art (Box 12)
  - EXP 045 F67 New Media of Creative Expression, 1967; UA044.003.012.00070 (Box 12)
  - EXP 045 F75 About Communicating, 1975; UA044.003.012.00071; Heims, Steve (Box 12)
  - EXP 045 F71 Introduction to American Popular Culture, 1971; UA044.003.012.00072; Carlson, Carl (Box 12)
  - EXP 045 F69 Art and Technology of Space, 1969; UA044.003.012.00073; Crystal, Curtis (Box 12)
  - EXP 046 F69 New Media of Creative Expression, 1969; UA044.003.012.00074 (Box 12)
  - EXP 046 F71 Intermediate to Advanced Technique, 1971; UA044.003.012.00075; White, Griselda (Box 12)
  - EXP 046S S75 The Art and Science of Food, 1975; UA044.003.012.00076; Brader, Donna; LaBarbera, Loring (Box 12)
  - EXP 047S S75 Lichen Ecology and Biology, 1975; UA044.003.012.00077; Ammerman, Seth (Box 12)
  - EXP 047S S73 Introduction to Amateur Radio, 1973; UA044.003.012.00078; Weiner, Jerry (Box 12)